When you calculate the area under a curve,
计算弧线下方区域时
what you're actually doing is taking an integral.
你实际上是在求积分
And the mathematical symbol for the integral is this stretched out "S" looking shape.
积分的数学符号看起来像一个拉长的 S
And often it'll have what are called bounds of integration at the bottom and the top.
在它的上方和下方给出了积分的界限
So, in this case, t1 is the lower bound and t2 is the upper bound.
因此 在本例中 t1 是下限 t2 是上限
And the integral is the opposite of the derivative.
积分和导数刚好相反
So, since velocity is the derivative of displacement,
因此 由于速度是位移的导数
this means that displacement is the integral of velocity. Let's go back to the graph.
这意味着 位移是速度的积分 我们再回到图表
Now remember that the area under this graph gives us the total displacement.
记住 图表下面的区域是总位移
Now I want to show you how to express this effect in integral notation.
下面 我们来看看如何使用积分来表示这个区域
The integral that expresses this exact same statement looks like this.
表示这个的积分表达是这样的
And the way I would read this is by saying delta x equals the
读起来就是 Δx 等于
integral from two to four of 100 dt. And that's a lot.
100 dt 从 2 到  的积分 这实际上很多
So, let me try to explain what this means.
我解释一下具体意思
It won't all be perfectly clear just yet, but that's okay for now.
可能还不能完全解释清楚 不过目前来说足够了
Total displacement.
总位移
Well, that we just represent with delta x.
我们使用 Δ x 表示
And that should be pretty familiar.
这应该很熟悉了
Let's take a look on the right-hand side.
我们看看右手边
Well, on the right-hand side we have this integral sign with the bounds of integration.
右手边 有一个积分符号 还有积分的界限
The 100 and the "dt" to the right of it.
右边是 100 和 dt
Let's talk about this "dt" for a second.
我们解释一下这个 dt
There's always going to be a "d something" in an integral,
积分中总会有 d 后面跟一些东西
and whatever that something is,
不管跟的是什么
in this case it's "t".
本例中 后面跟的是 t
It's just meant to tell you what these bounds of integration actually mean.
它实际上是告诉你积分界限具体指什么
So the fact that the something here is a "t", well,
这里 它指的是 t
it means that this lower bound of integration is t equals
也就是说 积分的界限下限是 t 等于
2 and not x equals 2 or v equals 2 or anything else.
2 不是 x 等于 2 或 v 等于 2 也不是任何其他内容等于  2
Now all that's left is this 100,
现在就剩下 100 了
and the reason this just happens to be a
这里刚好是 100
simple 100 is because the velocity function was so simple.
原因很简单 因为速度函数很简单
If on the other hand, the velocity function were more complicated,
如果速度函数更复杂一些
like let's say 50 plus 20 times t then, instead of 100,
比如 假设是 50 加上 20 乘以 t 那么这里就不是 100
we'd have 50 plus 20 times t. And in general,
而是 50 加上 20 乘以 t 一般来说
this v(t) can really be anything.
这里的 v(t) 可以是任何东西
So we can write this generic version of the
因此 我们用这个积分的通用版本
integral and this would work for any weird velocity function.
它可以用于所有奇怪的速度函数
Now if this all feels pretty overwhelming that's normal.
如果你觉得这很难 这很正常
For now I just wanted to introduce you to a notation that you're
现在 我们先知道这个式子
going to be seeing throughout your self-driving car career.
在你的无人驾驶车生涯中 你会不断碰到它
And fortunately, computers make using this notation pretty straightforward.
幸运的是 计算机可以直接使用这个式子